本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 红鼻子的UFO 王老猫 小飞鱼 华青墨 Cancy
校对： 小坏玩意儿   后期： 深影后期组
丹尼・希勒
Danny Hillier?
前情提要
你是谁
Who's this?
你应该去问警察
You should ask the police
欧洲隧道里发生了什么
what is happening in the Eurotunnel.
他们找到了一半国会议员
They found half an MP
一半妓女
and half a prostitute.
现在是英法联合调查 我们别无选择
他不靠谱
我喜欢记住我帮助过的人
I like to remember the people I help.
他们想杀了我
谁想杀了你
等等 你们不能把我留在这儿
Wait! Wait! You can't just leave me!
求求你 回来
You can't! Please, come back.
这只是开始
我们会离真相越来越近的
We shall all be getting closer to the truth.
我说的是现金
I said cash.
打一炮如何
How about cock?
我不收小额的"款项"
I don't take tiny instalments.
你兄弟怎么样
How's your brother?
你告诉他我们要结婚了吗
You told him we're getting married yet?
你别管我兄弟
You leave my brother alone.
他如果再花这么多时间
Tell him if he keeps spending so much time
在我的人身边转...
hanging around my bitches...
就要付出代价了
he's gonna have to start paying.
知道了 图帕克
Get you, Tupac.
这是南肯特 亲爱的 不是南洛杉矶
This is South Kent, my darling, not South LA.
其他人敢这样跟我说话 我会灭了他们
Anybody else spoke to me like that, I'd smash them up.
你灭了他们
You'd smash em up!
对 对 我会的
Yeah. Yeah, I would.
就喜欢你这样
Love you long time.
好了
Right.
抱歉让你久等了 丹尼
Sorry to keeping you waiting so long, Danny.
有事耽搁了
Something really important came up.
什么 比车里有炸弹还重要吗
What, more important than a bomb in a car?
根本没有炸弹
There was no bomb.
这是什么 联邦警察又介入了 是吗
What's this? We got a federal police force now, have we?
爱丽丝・瓦塞尔曼 法国警察
Elise Wassermann, French Police.
对 对 我知道你是谁
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, I know who you are.
说说那通电话
So tell us about the telephone call.
他说他在隧道里留了两具尸体
He said he left two bodies in the tunnel.
对 一个国会议员和一个妓女
Yeah. An MP and a whore.
那名妓女似乎坐过你的车
Your car was seen picking up that whore.
什么 什么时候
What? When?
去年七月
July last year.
去年七月 我在布拉格
July last year I was in Prague.
我不需要花钱找女人 就算如此
Besides, if I did pay for gash, which I don't have to,
我想我绝对不会看上
I think I'd aim a little bit higher
英国海港街道上的
than some crack-addled tart
那些残花败柳
off the streets of an English seaport.
怎么会有别人用你的车呢 还两次
How would anyone have access to your car? Twice?
我没有史酷比啊 亲爱的
Well, I haven't got a Scooby, love.
我们可以到外面谈谈吗
Can we have a word outside?
你一定很高兴有个法国人帮忙
You must be pleased to have the French on board.
她就像马其诺防线一样有用
She's about as useful as the Maginot Line, that one.
一战后为防德军入侵构筑的防线
我希望这条长裤大小合适 丹尼
I hope the trousers fit all right, Danny?
我们就找到这么一条干净的
The only clean ones we could find.
我要回法国了
I'm going back to France.
如果我不在那儿
Maybe he will calm down and stop showing off
他或许会冷静下来 不再炫耀
if I am not there.
好吧
All right.
我们会监听他的手机
We'll tap his phone
并远程监控他的电脑 以防...
and put a remote hack on his computers in case...
总探长在哪里 凶手上传了一个视频
Where's the DCI? The killer's put a video up.
奥利弗 快点过来 他上传了一个视频
已经有几千点击率了
我们确定服务器的位置了吗
正在查找
我在欧洲隧道留了两具尸体
一个大名鼎鼎的法国政客
和一个默默无闻的英国妓女
我把她们放在一起是要说明一个简单的道理
I brought them together to show a simple truth...
法律面前人人并不平等
There is no equality before the law.
这是我的第一条真理
That is my first truth.
还有四条即将揭晓
There are four still to come.
我肯定警察会竭尽全力地抓到我
这是他们在犯罪现场认真工作的画面
去隧道 找到这些摄像头
那里没有监控摄像头
There's no CCTV there.
他绝对有针孔相机
He must have hidden cameras.
- 头儿 - 什么
- Boss! - What?
他在这里
It's here.
你什么意思
What do you mean, it's here?
他入侵了英国警局 正在使用他们的服务器
关掉它 马上
Shut it down! Now!
弄清楚他是怎么做到的
Find out how he is doing it.
天哪
Christ!
给你们最后一个影像
One last image for you...
看 她像欧元区一样分崩离析了
Look, she comes apart like the Eurozone.
你注意到他的话了吗 "我留下第一条真理"
You notice what he said. "I left. My first truth."
圣经体
Biblical.
像某些旧约中的上帝
Like some Old Testament God.
带着四个即将揭晓的真相
With four more truths to come.
他想惩罚我们
He wants to punish us.
# 到我的怀抱里 #
Venez dans mes bras
# 靠近我 亲爱的 #
Closer to me, dear
# 你使我 #
Donnez-vous moi
# 抛开一切恐惧 #
Set aside all fear
# 红线一根 缠绕永远 #
Restons enlaces pour l'éternité
# 是的 你是我的 #
Yes, you shall be mine
# 直到时间的尽头 #
Till the end of time
隧道谜案 第一季第二集
"无疑 这是康斯坦丝的倒霉日
"Assuredly it was one of Constance's bad days,
在那些日子里 她察觉到
one of those days on which she felt that the tide of life
生命的潮汐已毫无顾忌地将她搁浅
had left her stranded in utter neglect.
唯有伯斯利镇
The sound of the Bursley Town
银奖乐队的歌声
Silver Prize Band aroused her
- 能把她从苦痛中唤醒" - 我要吃药
- from her suffering..." - I need my medicine now.
还没到时间
It's not really time.
太疼了
So much pain.
给你
Here you are.
谢谢
Thank you.
死者是玛丽・维伦纽夫吗
凶手是法国人还是英国人
什么时候开新闻发布会
那五条真理还有什么隐情吗
今晚有空吗 队长
服务器关闭了 但视频已在网上蹿红
司法部大发雷霆
不像是有组织犯罪
这安抚不了他们 我们得抓住罪犯
我知道
跟我们英国同仁怎么样
他话太多
好的 除此之外呢
他的车闻起来像条湿狗
三个摄像头 被安在了隧道管线里
- 调查员呢 - 没问题 在回来的路上
我去一趟维伦纽夫失踪的那家旅馆
- 听见了吗 - 遵命 长官
万福玛利亚 你充满圣宠 主与你同在
Hail Mary, full of Grace, the Lord is with thee,
你在妇女中饱受称赞
blessed art thou amongst women.
你的亲子耶稣同受赞颂 万福玛利亚
Blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus. Holy Mary,
为我们罪人的此时此刻
pray for us sinners now
和将死之时祈祷 阿门
and at the hour of our death. Amen.
嘿 苏
Hey, Suze.
劳拉呢
Where's Laura?
不知道 见客户去了吧
Don't know. With a client?
在网上看到你了 爸爸
Saw you on the web, Dad.
尸体分成两半的时候真酷
It's pretty awesome when the bodies just come apart.
是啊 他们说网络使人变得麻木
Yeah... and they say the internet de-sensitises people.
和你讲话的可人是谁
So who's the babe you're chatting with?
查克斯 他来过新年派对 记得吗
Chuks. Remember he came to the New Year's Party?
一个法国同事
A French colleague.
她叫什么
What's her name?
羊角面包
Fifi Croissant.
法国传统早餐
我也会选这个
Yeah? Well, I would.
你想太多了
There's a fairly large assumption behind that statement.
今晚想几点睡觉
What time would you like turndown this evening?
什么
What?
喜欢什么样的枕边巧克力
What sort of chocolate would you like on your pillow?
真好笑
Yeah, funny.
在维伦纽夫尸体伤口周围
我们发现了少量吉玛的血迹
吉玛身上却没有
他先把吉玛分尸 然后才是维伦纽夫
是的
同一时间 同一把锯
什么样的锯
屠宰牲畜的手锯
他在屠宰场干的
一手抬一具尸体很难办到
屠宰场可不是容易进去的地方
欧洲隧道也是
没错
照顾好自己 爱丽丝
吃点东西 注意休息 身体需要这些
我知道了
你睡得很沉
You sleep very deeply.
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
工作
Working.
你不能 就这么走进来
You can't just... walk in here.
这栋公寓是我给你弄到的 记得吗
I got you this flat, remember?
是啊 通过勒索出租屋管理员
Yeah, by blackmailing the lettings officer.
他不该拿公寓做性交易
He shouldn't trade council flats for sex.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
确保你没事
To make sure you're okay.
- 你有钱吗 - 有
- Do you have money? - Mm-hmm.
我找了份兼职
I've even got a part-time job.
如果那男人...
If that man...
拜托
Oh, please.
你还记得在特雷斯科岛度假的日子吗
Do you remember those holidays on Tresco?
他带我去钓鲭鱼
He took me spinning for mackerel.
它们从海中飞越而出
The colour of them in the air, green and silver,
在空中闪着银绿色的光
the sea flying off them.
它们翻腾起伏着
They were thrashing around...
头敲击着船底
their heads smacking against the bottom of the boat.
眼睛撞出了血
Bloody eyes.
我在船的一侧吐了
I was sick over the side of the boat.
他笑了
He laughed.
告诉我
Tell me.
我已经告诉你了
I've already told you.
跟我说说他眼中的神情
Tell me about the expression in his eyes.
我得走了
I have to go.
我会给你找个工作
I'll find a job for you.
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
离我的宿舍远点 离我姐妹远点
Stay away from my hostel... and stay away from my sister.
你的宿舍 你的姐妹
Oh, your hostel. Your sister.
听好了 慈善家先生
Check out Mr. Charity
你为什么不滚到非洲
Why don't you fuck off to Africa
给狮子普及艾滋病知识
and teach HIV awareness to the lions?
你以为能吓到我吗
Do you think you frighten me?
我是你能随便扇耳光的
Do you think I am one of the girls
那些姑娘吗
you can just slap about?
没错
Yeah.
你犯了个错误
That was a mistake.
我喜欢你的姐妹
You know, I like your sister.
她有独创性 有灵魂
She's original, she's got spirit...
而且她床上功夫不错
and she wriggles in bed.
正因为她在
And it's only because of her
你在码头才没被打倒
that you're not face-down in the harbour.
为什么这么敌对
So why all the hostility?
因为你得不到她吧
Is it 'cos you can't have her?
这就是我见到维伦纽夫女士的地方
会议过后她去公园走了走 清醒头脑
我们彻底搜过那个公园 没有证据和目击证人
你为什么会在马赛
我母亲病了
谢谢
女士 您还是什么都不要吗
不了 谢谢
玛丽・维伦纽夫收到过威胁吗
疯子的档案
什么样的疯子
极左极右的阴谋论者
"接种疫苗是犹太复国主义者政府的武器"
从他们对接种疫苗的态度能看出来谁是傻子
知道是谁炸了双子大楼吗
摩萨德 外星人 齐丹 齐达内 全在这里
我想可能是极右派 她想从他们那里获取选票
种族主义者的选票
我并不想这么称呼
- 为什么 - 因为这要比之复杂得多
通常人们越想逃避真相 事情就会变得越复杂
这个座位有人了
That seat's taken.
挺有洞察力啊
Very observant.
是你的吧
One of yours?
我的什么
One of my what?
我想在这地方
I'm guessing it easier
搞到一点可卡因应该比
to get a gram of stepped-on cocaine
搞到三明治要容易得多吧
in this place than a sandwich,
可是快午餐时间了
but it's nearly lunchtime,
我很饿 老二又疼
I'm very hungry and my balls are aching.
这是谁
Try again.
- 吉玛 - 不错
- Gemma. - Good.
吉玛・柯万
Gemma Kirwan.
- 不错 还有呢 - 还有什么
- Good. And? - And what?
她死了 你还有什么要跟我说的吗
And she's dead, so what else can you tell me?
跟 坦妮娅谈吧
Talk to Tania.
通常在多弗路能找到她
You'll usually find her up on the Dover Road.
她们经常吵架
They were spars.
我只知道这些
That really is all I can tell you.
我要找坦妮娅
I'm looking for Tania.
是坦妮娅吗
Tania?
我至今还没有坐过警车的
I haven't had a close encounter with the passenger seat
副驾驶呢 长官
of your Mondeo yet, officer.
坦妮娅 我可比别人要略胜一筹哦
I am a cut above the rest, Tania.
我们能谈谈吗 关于吉玛
Can we have a chat? About Gemma.
能去我的住所吗
Can we go to my place?
这是谁
Who is this?
我儿子 毛瑞西欧
It's my son... Mauricio.
你从没跟我提起过他
You didn't mention him.
这个重要吗
Does it make a difference?
刚才外面的那个男人 别再和他说话了
The man you were with outside, you must not talk to him.
他说会帮我找份工作
He said he would help me to find a job.
他是个粗暴的皮条客
He's a violent pimp.
他可能还会伤害到你的儿子的
He might hurt your son as well.
打包好你的东西
Pack your things.
你要把我们赶出去吗
Are you are throwing us out?
你只管收拾好就是
Pack your things.
那个是你男朋友吗
Is that your boyfriend?
斯蒂芬吗 他都没有吻过女孩子吧
Stephen? I don't think he's even kissed a girl.
他是上流人士 和你一样谈吐有礼
He's posh, talks nice, just like you.
我不是上流人士 我是有教养 差别大了去了
I'm not posh, I'm educated. Big difference.
我只觉得她母亲很可怜
It's the mum I feel sorry for.
她不停地去警局
She kept going to the Old Bill
说她女儿有危险
and saying how her daughter must be in danger,
你们却不采取保护措施
and you did nothing.
每周日同一时间 吉玛都会给她母亲打电话
Every Sunday, Gem would call her mum at the same time.
你们应该去查查通话记录
You could have checked the phone records,
就会知道出了问题
seen there must be something wrong.
她失踪之前情绪怎么样
What was her mood like before she disappeared?
挺好的 情绪高涨
Yeah, good. She was up.
她说她恋爱了
She said she'd fallen in love.
- 跟谁 - 她没说
- Who with? - Wouldn't say.
只说他头脑聪明
Only that he had a brain-shaped head
他们一起聊天
and they'd talk about stuff.
聊了什么
What sort of stuff?
你知道的 不公正之类的
You know, injustice and that.
政治上的东西
Political shit.
我们只当她开玩笑
We took the piss a bit.
说他根本就不存在
We said he didn't really exist,
但是她好像很认真
but she just got all serious
还说她不会告诉我们的
and said she couldn't tell us.
结果有天她就不见了
Then one day she was just gone.
你们报案了吗
Did you tell the police?
这是在她房间里找到的
It was in her room.
我们翻看过
We checked to see
想找到她有关去向的线索
if there was any clues about where she'd gone.
有没有提到...
Does it mention...?
正好写到那里就没有了
It stops at exactly that point.
他真的上传了一个尸体视频吗
Is it true he's put a video up and it shows the body?
是的
Yeah.
他还说这是想让大家知道没人会在乎
And he says this is all to show how nobody values
一个妓女的生命吗
the life of a prostitute?
是的
Yep.
我们一定赢不了 是吗
We really can't win, can we?
我看过一遍疯子的档案了
所有人的
包括极端的无政府主义宗教狂热分子
精神错乱的人
甚至还有个农场主只吃他自己种出来的东西
我已经按优先顺序排好放在USB里了
不相关的我就略过了
我要完整的
- 不用谢 - 你说什么
我说不用谢
难道你每次给我文件我都要说谢谢吗
不 一次就足够了
谢谢
真不错
不用担心下次 这次的还作数
好的
英国快递
你人真好
You're really kind.
你想听音乐吗 或者广播
Do you want some music on? The radio?
我也可以再给你读书
I could read to you again?
放张CD吧
Put a CD on.
# 我曾住在摩尔街 #
In Moore Street where I did dwell
我的亚瑟过去常唱这首歌 他的声音优美低沉
My Arthur used to sing this... Lovely deep voice he had.
# 我深爱着 #
I loved right well
# 他追求我 一生逝去 #
He courted me my life away
# 但如今和我一起 #
But now with me...
多傻的女孩啊 苏
Such foolish girls, eh, Suze?
满世界都是
World's full of them.
你的孩子怎么不多来看看你
Why don't your children come and visit you more?
他们有自己的生活...
They have their own lives...
自己的孩子...
Their children...
科林住在悉尼
Colin lives in Sydney,
我当然不能怪他
of course, so I can hardly blame him.
这不公平
It's not fair.
我很高兴有你陪我
Well, I'm glad I have you.
# 在常青藤上 #
...on an ivy tree...
我明天给你带食物来
I'll bring you food tomorrow.
我不喜欢这儿
I don't like it here.
你没有别的选择
You don't have an alternative.
那个男人让你处境危险
You're in danger from that man.
房子附近有匹马
There's a horse in the field around the house.
你喜欢马吗
Do you like horses?
谁都不能知道你在这儿
No one can know you're here.
孩子可以去花园玩
The boy is all right in the garden,
不然就别离开房子
otherwise don't leave the house.
当地农民并不同情
Local farmers are not exactly sympathetic
寻求庇护失败者
to failed asylum seekers.
晚上好
你还在上班啊
想喝点什么
你喜欢男人还是女人
- 通常是女人 - 你有女朋友吗
你有老公吗
没有
给我看看你的手
这证明不了什么 我可以把戒指摘掉
那你为什么那么做呢
因为我想和你上床
现在吗
我昨天去见丹尼・希勒了
I met Danny Hillier yesterday.
- 丹尼・希勒是谁 - 那个小报记者
- Who's Danny Hillier? - The tabloid journalist.
他写普通人的事儿 相当于他的一个标签
He writes about ordinary folk, sort of his catchphrase.
说明他讨厌移民
Ordinary for him means hating immigrants,
他们多用俚语 不学无术
talking in rhyming slang and not reading books.
- 听起来像统治者的工具 - 是
- Sounds like a tool of the highest order. - Yes, he is.
- 他应该见见爷爷 - 没错
- He should meet granddad. - Yes.
对那个老王八蛋来说没什么是正常的
Nothing ordinary about that old bastard, eh?
我不知道
I dunno.
你不知道什么
What don't you know?
他没扔下奶奶
Well, he didn't just leave grandma on her own
让她一个人带孩子
to bring up the kids,
所以至少他还是有正常的地方的
so there was something ordinary about him at least.
但他有点脾气
He had a bit of a temper on him though.
我话多的时候他会给我反手一下
Gave me a couple of backhanders when I got too mouthy.
- 是吗 - 是的 不过现在不流行了
- Yeah? - Yeah. It's gone out of fashion now.
卡尔
Karl!
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
你得洗碗
You're washing up.
好的 没必要像警察一样粗暴
All right, no need for police brutality.
意面很好吃 劳拉 谢谢
It was delicious pasta, Laura, thanks.
很高兴你喜欢它
I'm glad you liked it.
你跟他交谈方法要适当
You are going to have to talk to him properly.
让他洗更多的碗是没用的
Nothing will be solved by making him wash up more.
就这样吗
我得睡觉
你可以睡这啊 房间是空的
我现在要走 不过待会儿会回来
旁边有人我睡不着
但你却可以和一个人陌生人上床
你不是陌生人啊 我们之前见过
把你的戒指戴上吧
我没戒指
我只是不能接受旁边睡着个人
为什么不能
呼吸声太重 会吵到我
有人说过你很古怪吗
有 人们常常这么想
谢谢 很舒服
随时欢迎
真的
当然
好的
怎么了
What is it?
该死
Bloody hell.
卡尔 告诉奥贝里克斯我想杀了她
Karl, tell Obelix that I'll bloody kill her.
法国英雄
嗨 爱丽丝
Hi, Elise.
你觉得在一个自产自销的有机农场
What would you expect to find
能找到什么
on a self-sufficient organic farm?
什么 便鞋吧 现在都几点了
What? Birkenstocks. What time is it?
有人生产并屠宰自家的猪
Somebody who produces and butchers their own meat
因为他们憎恶
because they hate
犹太复国主义的法国政府
the Zionist Occupied Government of France.
- 直说吧 - 我觉得我找到了一个屠宰场
- Just tell me. - I think I have found a slaughterhouse.
我要去一探究竟
I'm going to check it out.
有可能就在
It might be on the farm of a man
威胁玛丽・维伦纽夫那人的农场里
who threatened Marie Villeneuve.
他叫乔尔・摩金
His name is Joel Mougin.
等等...听着...那个...
Wait... Look... Just...
我不会有事的 我只是想确认是否有这么个人
I'll be fine. I just want to see if it has one.
别动 否则我打爆你的头
我是刑侦大队的瓦塞尔曼队长 我有证件
证件没用
你想知道里面有什么
走啊 进去看
别拘束
谁让你来的
瓦瑟曼 是犹太语啊
名字是
- 你有犹太血脉? - 我不懂那代表什么
我父亲家是犹太人 我母亲是天主教徒
对我来说这不重要
继续走
他们知道
知道来这儿就会死
他们恐慌了
闻到了死亡的味道
继续走
那是什么
别动
你的屠宰场怎么有半具尸体
我不知道 一周前还没有
你是说是别人干的
是的
这些是你发给玛丽・维伦纽夫的吗
不瞒你说
我觉得她死不足惜
- 摩金先生 - 她不是犹太人
她给犹太复国主义政府做事
就是那个给我们的肉下毒的人?
是 尽管笑吧
我没有笑
I am not laughing.
什么
这就是你所认为的法律面前的不平等?
What is your view of inequality before the law?
这婊子说什么呢
喂
Yup.
你好 丹尼
Hello, Danny.
我知道你是谁
I know who this is.
警方抓住的那个人
The man the police are holding
只是个白痴纳粹
is only guilty of being a cretinous Nazi.
我确定他甚至不知道
I'm sure he doesn't even know
玛丽・维伦纽夫有个小伤疤
Marie Villeneuve had a little scar
在她左胸下
under her left breast,
或者吉玛・柯万爱她妈妈
or that Gemma Kirwan loved her mother.
你真是个变态 你知道吗
You're a sick fuck, you know that?
那辆车的小把戏...
That stunt with the car...
我选择乐呢
I have chosen you.
我要人们知道我为何如此行事
I want people to know why I am doing this.
- 那不是他 - 你甚至还没审问他
他不说英语 而且着迷于对犹太人的憎恨
摩金不会让法律的不平等作为他的第一条真理
凶手在利用他的屠宰场 要么就是想误导我们
凶手又给那个记者打电话了
我回去了
我选择了你
I have chosen you.
我要人们知道我为何如此行事
I want people to know why I'm doing this.
他在尽力教我们
He's trying to teach us.
他想展示暴露我们的道德弱点
He wants to demonstrate his superiority
给他带来的优势
by exposing our moral weakness.
我儿子就有一点儿这个作风
My son's a bit like that.
他决定做个素食主义者
He just decided to become a vegetarian.
我姐姐也是
My sister, too.
那张照片 你说对了
You were right about the photograph.
曼侬是我的双胞胎姊妹
Manon was my twin.
她淹死了
She drowned.
你应该会喜欢她的 她很有趣
You would have liked her. She was funny.
杀手特意说他选择了你
The killer said specifically that he has chosen you.
他为什么这么做
Why would he do that?
或者他是我工作的粉丝
Maybe he's a fan of my work.
被脑残的追随者包围了是吧
Round up the mindless bigot's then, eh?
看到你带着如此轻蔑的态度
It's nice to see you hold the ordinary working class folk
去从事民间最普通的工作 真好
with such contempt.
你可以回答我的问题吗
Can you answer my question?
有什么用
What's the point?
很明显你已经拿到录音了
You've already got the tapes, obviously.
他为什么选中了你
Why did he choose you?
老实说 我不知道
Je ne sais fucking pas, honestly.
下次试着拖延时间 问他问题
Keep him talking next time, ask him questions.
这是什么 第三帝国?
What is this, the Third Reich?
我是个记者 我不需要接受你们的...
I'm a journalist,I don't need to take orders from...
我们在你车里发现了两克可卡因
We found two grams of cocaine in your car.
要问哪种问题
What sort of questions?
问他想要什么 他做这个想得到什么
Ask him what he wants. What he hopes to gain by this.
问得模糊不清 让他说话
Keep it vague. Keep him talking.
你好
Hello.
是的 和他在一块儿
Yeah, with him now.
什么时候
When?
好的
Okay.
你介意去查一下你的收件箱吗
Would you mind checking your inbox?
喝下我
老人有什么用 他们不事生产
What good are old people? They do not produce.
他们除了消费我们的税金别无他物...
They consume nothing except our taxes...
所以我们让他们独自死去
so we leave them to die alone.
# 他追求我 一生逝去 #
He courted me my life away
# 如今他不再和我一起 #
But now with me he will not stay
# 我祈祷 我徒劳地祈祷 #
I wish, I wish, I wish in vain
# 希望我能重获青春 #
I wish I were a maid again
# 但是光阴一去不复返 #
But a maid again I'll never be...
马尔梅德养老院 人们在死去
Malmead House. People are dying.
# 直到樱桃 #
Till cherries grow
# 长在常青藤上 #
On an ivy tree...
喂
Yeah?
是他 开始行动了
It's him. He's started.
# 他走上楼 撞开门 #
He went upstairs and the door he broke
# 发现她吊在绳子上 #
He found her hanging by a rope
# 他拿出刀 将绳子割断 #
He took his knife and he cut her down
# 在她的口袋里 找到了这样的字条 #
And in her pocket these words he found
# 把我的坟墓建得宽敞幽深 #
Oh, make my grave large, wide and deep...
苏
Suze.
你能听到吗 苏 你吃了什么
Can you hear me? Suze, what have you taken?
斯蒂芬
Stephen.
不 我是安东尼 宝贝
No, it's Anthony, babe.
你给我打了电话 你吃了什么
You called me. What have you taken?
# 其间有一个斑鸠 #
And in-between a turtle dove
# 这样全世界都知道 我为爱而死 #
That the world may know I died for love